* 	 (HEAD -> master, origin/master) URL is appended while toggling with tabs in a modal
* 	 Some files changed, but UI is still buggy
* 	 Quill Text editor files added
* 	 Diary Page added in UI
* 	 Cards added in excercises page
* 	 Grids added in Exercises
* 	 Extras page removed
* 	 Pages added
* 	 Login modal's UI changed properly and now its final
* 	 Login and register model added in UI
* 	 NavBar and HEro sectionadded
* 	 MDB NavBar added
* 	 Frontend in react
